In the first part of this program,
在本课程的第一部分
we'll cover the main algorithms of supervised and unsupervised learning,
我们将介绍监督学习和非监督学习的主要算法
as well as the main techniques for making your models work well.
以及使模型运行良好的主要技巧
In the first section called Model evaluation and validation,
在第一部分 即模型评估和验证
you will learn what machine learning models are and how to train them,
你将学习什么是机器学习模型以及如何训练模型
test them and validate them.
测试模型和验证模型
You will learn the main problems one has to deal with when training a model,
你将学习在训练模型时需要解决的主要问题
such as: over fitting and under fitting.
例如过拟合与欠拟合
And you'll be able to measure them and improve your training.
你将能够衡量模型并改善训练效果
Most algorithms of machine learning fall into two categories,
大多数机器学习算法都分为两大类
supervised learning and unsupervised learning.
监督学习和非监督学习
Supervised learning is comprised of all the algorithms which will predict a label.
监督学习由所有预测标签的算法组成
We'll go deep into the algorithms of supervised learning such a decision trees,
我们将深入了解监督学习的算法 例如决策树
logistic regression, support Vector machines,
逻辑回归 支持向量机
Naive Bayes and neural networks.
朴素贝叶斯和神经网络
In the next section, you will be learning the main unsupervised learning algorithms,
在下个部分 你将学习主要非监督学习算法
especially those involving clustering and dimensionality reduction.
尤其是涉及到聚类和降维的算法
These are useful when our data comes with
如果我们的数据没有标签 并且我们需要发现数据特性
no labels and we need to find properties about it.
这些算法就很有用
You'll be able to apply these algorithms on real data sets as well.
你还将有机会将这些算法应用到实际数据集上
In the second part of the nanodegree program,
在纳米学位课程的第二部分
you will go much deeper into cutting edge topics in machine learning,
你将深入学习机器学习的前沿技术
such as; Deep learning and reinforcement learning.
例如深度学习和强化学习
Neural networks have been crucial in most of
神经网络对于最近的大部分机器学习
the recent advances in machine learning including Alpha go,
发展动态来说都非常关键 包括 Alpha go
IBM Watson and self driving cars.
IBM Watson 和无人驾驶汽车
In the next section, you'll get a solid foundation of deep neural networks.
在下个部分 你将掌握扎实的深度神经网络基础知识
You'll also learn convolutional neural networks use from many applications,
还将学习卷积神经网络在很多领域的应用
but in particular, for image recognition.
尤其是图片识别
Reinforcement learning is an interesting form of machine learning
强化学习是一种有趣的机器学习形式
where do you train an intelligent agent to perform actions in an environment,
你会训练智能体在环境中执行操作
Instead of predicting labels or values.
你将不再预测标签或值
You'll get to use state of the art platforms,
而是使用先进的平台
like open the EyeGym and cutting edge deep reinforcement
（例如 OpenAI EyeGym 和深度 Q 网络等前沿性深度强化学习算法）
learning algorithms like deep Q-networks to solve challenging problems.
解决具有挑战性的问题
After completing this program,
学完本课程后
you'll have a solid foundation in the main algorithms used in machine learning today.
你将充分理解在现今的机器学习领域使用的主要算法
See you in class.
稍后见